I hate scary movies
我最讨厌恐怖片
I should be studying You know I got a bio due
我得看书 我要交生物作业
Baby，did I mention these tickets are free？
我不是说过 票是免费的吗？
Free
免费的
Sandra Bullock is playing right down the street
珊卓·布拉克的电影也在上映
Nobody will pay seven fifty to see some Sandra Bullock shit
没人要花250元看布拉克
Unless she is naked
除非她裸体
But you will sit through a movie called 「Stab」？
你却会想看没大牌的
Adrenaline，Maureen
「失声尖叫」 刺激肾上腺素
It is good to be scared。It is primal。You know what I'm saying
惊吓可刺激起人类本能
No，I'm gonna tell you what it is。Okay？
我来告诉你这是什么电影
It's a dumb ass white movie about some dumb ass white girls…
就是无聊白人女孩被追杀
getting their white asses cut the fuck up，okay？
一部无聊的白人被追杀的电影
Yeah，and I suppose Sandra Bullock is miss ethnicity？Right？
你以为珊卓·布拉克是黑人啊？
No，I'm saying that the horror genre is historical for excluding…
恐怖片向来排斥黑人
the African-American element
When did you get your PHD in black cinema，sister soldier？
你几时拿到黑人电影博士学位
Listen，I read my 「Entertainment Weekly」，I know my shit
我有看「娱乐周刊」 我知道
Yeah，Maureen，I read my 「Black Beat」 too，homey
我也看「黑人电影圈」
Are you going to have a all-black movie？Black-cast？All-black wardrobe
你要全黑的电影？黑人卡司
Black-eyes peas？Black cats？
黑眼珠？黑猫？
Hi，here you go…
嘿 拿着
What's this？
这是什么？
「Stab」 souvenirs，studio sent them
纪念品 片厂送的
And it's white，thanks
白色的耶 谢谢
Very romantic
真有够浪漫
So，why does she got to be naked？What does that have to do…
她干嘛非得裸体？
with the plot of the story her being butt-ass naked
她光溜溜的 关剧情什么事
Well，I don't know about the plot but I have got a stiffy
那我倒不知道 我勃起了
You better loosen up that wrist
自己打手枪吧
Hello？
喂
Hello
Who is this？
哪位？
Guess
你猜
No，really，who is this？
不 真的 哪位？
Were you expecting somebody？
你在等人吗？
No
没有
Bitch，hang the phone up and 「star-69」 his ass！
蠢货 挂他电话
Who is this？
哪一位？
Who would you like it to be？
你希望是谁？
I don't like games。Who is this？
我不喜欢玩游戏 哪位？
Look out back Do you see your boyfriend anywhere？
看后面 看到你男朋友没？
I don't even have a boyfriend right now
我现在没男朋友
Would you like one？
想要一个吗？
Give me some money I need to get some popcorn
给我钱 我要买爆米花
You got money
你自己有钱
I got 「my」 money I asked for your money
那是我的钱 我要你的钱
What do you say？
你说好不好？
Come on。Cat got your tongue？
快啊怎么不说话
You know，I don't even know you and I dislike you already
我还不认识你 就不喜欢你了
Hey，we're sold out
嘿 卖光了
Hi。Can I have a medium popcorn no butter。And a small diet Pepsi
中的爆米花 一杯小健怡可乐
You got it
好的
That's it I am not going back in there
够了 我不回里面去
Come on，you chicken shit it's just a movie
胆小鬼 只是电影嘛
Not it's not just a movie It's a true story
这不只是电影 这是真实故事
All these kids got killed a couple of years ago in California
这些人几年前 在加州被杀
You ass！
好讨厌
I'm sorry，I had to，baby
对不起 我只想吓你
Why are you playing？
你干嘛要吓我
Would you relax？
别紧张
I don't like being scared I don't like that
我不喜欢被吓 我不喜欢
Baby，it's just a movie
宝贝 只是电影嘛
Besides scary movies are great foreplay
而且恐怖片 是很棒的前戏
Excuse me？
拜托！
Let's go see Sandra Bullock
我们去看珊卓·布拉克好了
No，Sandra's started already We can stay
不 都开演了 留下吧
Just stop playing so much
你别这么爱闹就好了
Alright I have to go to the bathroom
好 我要上厕所
See you inside
里面见
Sorry
对不起
Hello？
有人吗？
No，no！Don't do that
不…别那么做
Move，move… Go
快 快 走啊
Baby，give it up
宝贝 别闹了
You came back just in time，it looks like she's just about to get it
回来得正好 她快被杀了
Want some popcorn？
要爆米花吗？
If that was me，I'dbe out of there
换成是我 我会离开那边
Here it comes
来了
《惊声尖叫2》
Hello
喂
Hello，Sidney
喂 西德妮
Who this is？
哪位？
What's your favorite scary movie？
你最喜欢哪部恐怖片？
Who is this？
哪位？
You tell me
你告诉我啊
Cory Gillis，5550176
科瑞·吉利斯 5550176
Shit
妈的
hot flash，Cory
别气馁 科瑞
Call criminal offense prosecutor on the penal code 653M
你可以找刑事检察官
Hope you enjoy the movie
希望你喜欢「失声尖叫」
Time to change numbers again
又要换号码了？
No，it will die off。It's opening weekend。Let's see how it goes
会熬过去的 周末才上映呢
Okay
好
You know，Ron
你知道 罗恩
It's not an easy thing to be accused of a crime you didn't commit
被冤枉犯罪一定不好受
Particularly one as heinous as murder
尤其是谋杀 这么恐怖的罪
But how do people treat you now that they know the truth…
真相大白后 大家怎么对待你
about your innocence
关于你的清白
Most people are good
大半人都不错
There are still some that keep a safe distance
有些人还是保持距离
which is odd for me 'cause I've always been sort of a people person
我觉得很奇怪 毕竟我一向是个平凡人
You were wrongly accused You were fully exonerated
你被冤枉 现已宣判无罪
That and a nickel gets you a cup of coffee
曾经被判有罪的人
Even that's not true anymore
要完全洗刷清白 不太容易
Certainly with Gale Weather's book and now the movie…
盖尔的书 还有电影
it sets the record straight for Cotton Weary
洗刷了卡顿·威瑞的冤情
One would think Gale has been terrific through all this…
大家可能会觉得 盖尔够意思
Hey！Move your ass，you're late
快点 要迟到了
And don't forget about the routine mixer and the Delta Lambda Zeta
别忘了固定的聚会
I don't think I'll be able to make it，Hal
我看我去不了了
What！Don't even try to bag you promised me
什么？别想翘头 你答应过
A vague promise at best
随便答应而已
Nobody's asking you to join。It's a party。Free beer，meet the girls
这是免费啤酒 交朋友的派对
Hallie，you know me and organized religion
你知道我不太喜欢 宗教聚会
It's a sorority…
这是姐妹会
Worse
那更糟
Look Sid，lower the walIs for the next few days
你不要太孤僻
This self-induced isolation you got going is not healthy
孤立自己不太好
I'm fine
我没事
I'm fine。Yeah，I know
是 我知道
I'm fine is stretched tightly across your face
说没事却绷着个脸
Check out the news
赶快看新闻
The two Windsor college students were murdered last night…
两名温莎学院的学生
during a sneak preview of the new movie，「Stab」
昨晚看「失声尖叫」时遇害
Police have not released any infor- mation except for the victims names
警方目前只公布被害人姓名
But a press conference has been scheduled later today
但今晚稍后将举行记者会
The victims，Maureen Evens & Phil Stevens were both Windsor seniors
两名被害人皆为大四学生
Where's Randy？
兰迪在哪儿？
He's got film theory this morning
他早上有电影理论课
Sidney
西德妮
Did you know the victims？
你认识被害人吗？
Did you feel threatened by the murders？
这些命案对你造成威胁吗？
Do you think they'll be more murders？
你想会发生更多命案吗？
What can you tell us about the victims，Sid？
告诉我们有关被害人的事
We just need one statement
发表一点意见好吗？
You could say what happened in that theater…
电影剧情造成 戏院谋杀事件
is a direct result of the movie itself
是对电影本身的直接结果
That is so moral majority
这样子的说法太假道学了
You can't blame real life violence on entertainment
现实生活的暴力不能怪娱乐
Yes，you can Don't you even watch the news？
当然可以 你不看新闻吗？
Hello？The murderer was wearing a Ghost mask
拜托 凶手戴电影的鬼面具
Just like in the movie It's directly responsible
不怪电影怪谁
No，it's not。Movies are not responsible for our actions
电影不该为我们的行为负责
It's a classic case of life imitating art，imitating life
但电影是模仿现实的伟大艺术
This is not a hypothetical It's not about that
凶杀案不该模仿 更不是艺术
I had biology with that girl This is reality
死者是我的同学 这是现实世界
Thank you，I agree with you
谢谢 我同意
Let me tell you about reality Mickey
我告诉你们什么是现实
I lived through this，okay？
我亲身经历过 好吗？
Life is life It doesn't imitate anything
现实生活是不能被模仿
Come on，Randy。With all due respect the killer obviously pattered…
少来了 兰迪
himself，after two serial killers who have been immortalized on film
凶手显然在仿效 杀人狂角色
Thank you
谢谢
Are you suggesting that someone is trying to make a real life sequel？
你是说有人想演出续集？
Stab 2？Who would wanna do that Sequel's suck
谁想那么做？续集都很烂
Oh，please，please。By definition alone，they're inferior films
就字意看 续集就是二等的
Bullshit generalization。Many sequeIs have surpassed their originals
胡扯 很多续集成绩超越原片
Oh yeah？Name one
举例一部
「Aliens」 Far better than the first
异形续集就比第一集好很多
Yeah there's no accounting for taste
是啊你品味真有够差
Thank you。Ridley Scott rules Name another
谢谢 再举一部
Aliens is a classic，okay
异形是经典电影
「Get away from her，you Bitch」
「离她远点 贱货」
I believe the line is 「Stay away from her，you Bitch」
拜托 正确台词是：「别靠近她 贱货」
This is film class right？
这才是电影里的意思
Whatever，you know what I mean
好 随便 你懂我意思
Another…T-2
魔鬼终结者2
You got a hard on for Cameron
你很爱卡麦隆是不是
A big one
爱疯了
Wait a second the first Terminator is historical
第一集已是老掉牙的历史
「Sarah Conner」 「Yes」
莎拉·康纳
Alright，alright 「House 2」 the second story
好 好 《恐怖屋续集》
The entire horror genre was destroyed by sequels
所有的恐怖片都被续集破坏了
I got it by the way，I got it
有了 有了
The Godfather Part 2
教父2
That's very good An Oscar Winning Exception
很好 获得金像奖的例外
Alright，that's enough That will be a wrap
好 够了 今天到此为止
The sequel discussion to be continued
下次再继续探讨续集
So，Mister Originality how would you make it different
创意先生 你如何使续集成功
I would let the geek get the girl
要让结局大爆冷门
Three hundred people watching and nobody did anything
三百个人在戏院里 没人去救
They thought it was a publicity stunt。For Christ's sake
他们以为是宣传 天哪
And it would have been a good one too
如果是宣传 这点子可精彩极了
It's starting again，Randy
兰迪 事情又开始了
It's not Shit happens at the movies
不 看电影才会碰到倒霉事
People get robbed，shot maimed，murdered
被抢变残废被谋杀
The multiplex is just very dangerous place be these days
影城现在是很危险的地方
You're in extreme denial
你不要每件事都否定它
And you should be too This has nothing to do with us
你也该这样 这跟我们无关
Randy。A guy in a Ghost mask hacked up two people in a movie theater
戴面具的人在戏院 砍了两个人
in a movie theater telling our life stories
在我们的生活里
Coincidence
只是巧合
You know what happened in Woodsboro Randy。You can't ignore it
你不能当做没事发生
I know Sid。I don't wanna go back there again
我知道 我不再重蹈覆辙
Can't we just go back to our pseudo-quasi happy existence？
我们不能假装快乐的生活吗
Hello Derek，how you doing？
德瑞克 你好
Sid，I've been looking everywhere
西德妮 我到处找你
I heard，you weren't in class
我听说了 你没去上课
Yeah，I know。I couldn't take all the 「that's her」 looks
我受不了「众所瞩目」的感觉
Is there anything I can do？
有什么我能做的？
You have any tricks to take us back to a pseudo-quasi happy existence？
教我如何假装快乐的生活
You know I just might have one for that
有个办法
Oh yeah，what is it？
是吗？是什么？
That was pretty good
这满不错的
Get a room
去开房间啦
They're threatening what？Are you kidding me？
他们威胁要怎样？别开玩笑
It would be stupid to pull this movie
让电影下片太蠢了
All this free press，they're going to have huge numbers this weekend
免费宣传 这个周末会大卖
It'll break box office records
它会打破卖座记录
Consider it done
没问题
Miss Weathers！Hi。I'm Joel the affiliate sent me
韦瑟斯小姐 嗨 我是乔
I'm the new cameraman
新来的摄影师
You got experience？
有经验吗？
Yeah，I'm local but I shot the Bingo Finals。Almost got an award for that
我拍过宾果总决赛 差点得奖
Alright。Listen Joel this is how it works
好 我告诉你怎么做
I point，you shoot
我指示你就拍
You stay focused and fast on your feet。And we'll get along fine
要专注 动作要快
You're playing with the big boys now。You got it？
你现在是专业摄影师
Got it。Got you covered。I'm all over it。Don't worry…
知道了 没问题
about a thing。How hard can it be？You point & I shoot。I'm there
安啦 能有多难嘛 你指我拍
Excuse me，Miss Weathers？Could I have a minute
对不起 韦瑟斯小姐 打搅一分种
No… Just one second？
不喔 只要一秒种
I know you probably get this all the time
我知道你常碰到这种事
But I just wanted to say that I'm such a big fan of your work
我是你的忠实书迷
I just finished your book。I couldn't put it down。lnsightful，probing
我刚看完你的书 爱不释手
I just really really loved your book
我爱死你的书了
Thank you
谢谢
I'm a writer myself。I write for the local paper for The Post Telegraph
我帮本地的报纸写东西
Debbie Salt
黛比·索特
I took your seminar in Chicago last year
我去年参加过 你的研讨会
I was the one in the front row asking all the questions
我坐在前排一直发问
I thought you looked familiar
难怪你很面熟
Thank you Can't wait to see the movie
谢谢 我迫不及待想看到电影
You know，you must be getting quite a lot of flak on that。Right？
你一定受到很多指责
W/ all the violence & cinema issues What is your position going to be？
你怎么看暴力与电影的关系
No comment
不予置评
It would be such an honor for me If I could just get a quote…
我很希望能引述你说的话
from you for my story
从我们的故事
Alright，begin quote
好 开始引述
Your flattering remarks are both desperate and obvious。End quote
你的马屁拍得太明显了
What are you doing here？Do you think these murders are connected？
你想这些命案有关连吗？
What's your theory on these murders？What's your feeling on this？
你对命案有什么看法？
Can I have your attention
对不起
My name if Chief Louis Hartley
我是哈利警长
Chief Hartley
哈利警长
Hi，Gale Weathers author of the Woodsboro Murders
盖尔 伍兹伯勒血案的作者
Do you think the killer will strike again？
你想凶手会再犯案吗？
We have no evidence that this is a serial killer
没证据显示 这是个连续杀人狂
I'dlike to read from a…
我想读一篇…
Can you tell us of any precautions that you are taking？
请问你们有任何 预防措施吗？
First of all，we think it's just an isolated incident
我们认为这是独立的案件
And we will be caring out many possibilities
我们会留意很多可能性
Oh my God，this is huge
我的天 事情大条了
Do you have any suspects？
有嫌犯了吗？
Sidney，look，it's Gale Weathers
西德妮 你看 盖尔
What？
什么？
Starring in the Gale Weathers Press Conference
盖尔的记者会
based on the book by Gale Weathers
盖尔的书
Soon to be a major motion picture starring Gale Weathers
她将主演盖尔的电影
Be kind，she saved our lives
别太毒了 她救过我们
She had calf-implants
她脑袋秀逗了
Chief Hartley，do you have plan on giving the town a curfew？
你打算实施宵禁吗？
I'm gonna get closer
我要去听她说什么
So that's her？
她就是盖尔？
Yeah
对
Hello girls，enjoying yourselves？
女孩们 你们还好吧？
Hello，Sister Lois Sister Murphy
洛伊斯姐妹 墨菲姐妹
Hi，Sidney
嗨 西德妮
This must be flat out hell for you How are you holding up？
感觉很可怕吧？撑得住吗？
I manage
我尽量
It's weird，isn't it？To think this fuss is all because of you
真奇怪 为了你 搞得鸡飞狗跳
I mean not directly。But in some six degrees of Kevin Bacon way
真是基努·里维斯的连锁反应
Are you going to bring your friend to our little martini mixer tonight？
海莉 你会带你朋友 来聚会吧
I have a lot of work to…
我有很多功课…
We'll be there
我们会到
Good，Because Sid we have our eyes on you
很好 我们会看着你的
You hang in there，and if there is anything we can do…
坚强点 入会后 就是一家人了
the Delta lambaste are very sensitive to your plight
就是一家人了
Yeah…Bye
对 再见
You going to start to dress like that when you get in？
你入会后要穿成那样吗？
That's not going to happen
杀了我吧！
The Delta Lambdas are the biggest bunch of fucking…
DL姐妹会是一群臭…
I'm pledging Delta Lambda thank you
我要入会 谢谢你哦
Oh my God
我的天
Who's that？
那是谁？
Dewey？
杜威
What are you doing here？
你在这儿做什么？
I was worried about you
我很担心你
I heard about what happened I was on the next plane
事情一发生我就搭机赶来
Can we talk？
可以谈谈吗？
Yeah，yeah
好啊
Are you okay？
你还好吗？
I'm fine，Dewey
我很好
Or was… Things were okay Until now
事情发生前都很好
The theater's going great。I got my first starring role，open in two days
不过我主演的戏 两天后公演
That is great
太棒了
Yeah，I'm loving it And I've got some great friends
对 我很高兴还有很多好朋友
And I'm seeing someone
我交了个男朋友
Nice guy，pre-med no apparent psychotic tendencies
他念医科 没精神错乱倾向
I was just worried
我只是担心
Look Sid，if there is some freaked out psycho trying to follow in…
如果有变态狂想跟随
Billy Loomis' footsteps
比利·鲁米斯的脚步
You probably already know him Or her
你八成已经认识他…或她
or them
或他们
They're probably already in your life
他们才不会放过你
They get off on that
从你的生活中可以得到刺激
I just want you to be careful，Sid.
你要小心
You think I don't know that
我怎么会不清楚？
What am I suppose to do？
可是我能怎么办？
Cut everybody off crawl under a rock？What？
跟每个人断绝关系躲起来
Just watch out Keep an eye out
当心点就是了
I'm going to talk to Chief Hartley and the local police
我去跟哈利警长谈一谈
I'm going to just hang around I want to make sure you're safe
我会留下来注意你的安危
If that's alright with you？
可以吗？
Yeah
好
Hey，you okay？
没事吧
Who was that guy？
那个人是谁？
An old friend
老朋友
Deputy Dewey。Woodsboro's finest What's he doing here？
伍兹伯勒的副警长 他来干嘛
He's worried Our surrogate big brother
他担心我 就像我们的大哥哥
Nothing like a funeral to bring the family together
葬礼最能让家人团聚
I'm going to go say Hi
我去打招呼
Chief Hartley said the girl was stabbed seven…
哈利警长说 那女孩被刺七刀
Drop it
别说了
Hello，Sidney，how are you？
西德妮 你好吗？
Hi，what do you want，Gale？
嗨 什么事？
I was hoping I might get a few words with you
我希望跟你谈几句话
Cotton…
卡顿
Hi，Sidney
嗨 西德妮
Here we are at Windsor College where Sidney Prescott has just…
这里是温莎学院 在此 西德妮与卡顿…
be united with Cotton Weary for the first time since she wrongly…
自她曾误控他谋杀她母亲后…
accused him of murdering her mother
首度重逢
What the hell are you doing？
你在干什么？
We want to know how you feel？
我们想知道你的感受
Tell us everything that has happened Looking back on the last two years
告诉我们你这两年的情形
Sidney，I'djust like to say that I forgive and forget
我想说我原谅你 也忘了过去
Just like you，I'dlike to get back on with my own life
和你一样我只想好好过日子
Do you have any comments？
你有任何话要说吗？
You bitch
贱货
Sidney，share with us please
西德妮 请跟我们分享
I'll share with you
我会跟你分享的
Okay，okay，okay
好 好 好
Did you get that on film？
拍下来没？
Yes，I got that on film
拍下来了
Sid？Wait，wait where's she going，Gale？Sidney？
西德妮 等等 她去哪？西德妮
Where's she going？
她去哪里？
Gale，I thought we had an official interview。What's going on？
不是正式访问吗？怎么回事
She didn't know？
她不知道？
That was cold…
真冷酷
You need to check your conscious at the door，sweetie
您需要在检查门口 搞清楚
We're not here to be loved
我们不是来讨人喜欢的
Gale，you promised me ten minutes of national coverage
你答应我十分钟的全国报导
You'll get your ten minutes when I get my God damned interview
等我访问到你就有 他妈的十分钟报导
Don't walk away from me，Gale I'm still…
别掉头就走 我还…
Gale，I did my part
我做了我该做的部份
Joel
乔
Dewey。What are you doing here？
杜威 你怎会出现在这里？
Why don't you just leave her alone
你为什么不放过她
Hasn't she been through enough？
她受的还不够吗？
And my name is Dwight
还有 我的名字是德威
I'm just doing my job，Dwight
我只是做我份内的事
No matter who gets hurt in the process
任何人受伤都没关系吗？
Who got punched here，again
是谁又挨了一拳？
I don't condone violence but maybe you deserved it
我也不喜欢暴力 可是你活该
Page thirty-two
在书中第32页 你写到
Deputy Dewey filled the room with his Barney Fifish presence
「笨手笨脚的杜威副警长」
You read my book
你看过我的书
Yes，I do read，Miss Weathers
我常看书 韦瑟斯小姐
Dewey，don't take it so seriously It's just a character in a book
别生气 那只是书中人物
Page forty-one Deputy Dewey oozed with inexperience
41页 副警长很没经验
Don't you think you're overacting just a little bit？
你不觉得你反应过度吗？
No，what I think is you're a money-hungry，fame-seeking…
不 我觉得你是个贪图名利的
and forgive me for saying mediocre writer
二流作家
who has a cold storage shed where her heart should be
你根本没血没眼泪
No offense intended
别见怪
Dewey，I never meant to imply…
我不是故意的…
How do you know my dimwitted inexperience isn't merely a subtle…
你怎么知道我没经验
form of manipulation used to lower people's expectations thereby…
难道你是故意贬低我
enhancing my ability to effectively maneuver within any given situation？
免得观众对我期望太高？
I'm sorry
对不起
I don't know what else to say Except，I'm sorry
除了抱歉我不知道该说什么
No。I'm the one that's sorry I misjudged you
我才抱歉 我看错你了
Now，if you'll excuse me I have some oozing to do
失陪 我去执行 我的瘪三警察任务
One more thing。Nice streaks
还有一件事 头发染得不错
I am not a sorority pusher
我不是强迫推销姐妹会的人
I just think despite its trivialities
我只是觉得这是个肯定人生
it's a life affirming，mentally stable healthy environment for you
稳定心理的健康环境
Look at this place
看看这个地方
I think you're talking your psych-major a little too seriously，Hallie
你心理学修得太过火了
I'm fine
我没事
That's beginning to become your theme song。I'm fine
「我没事」变成你的口头禅了
Yeah，fucked up，lnsecure Neurotic and Emotional
没安全感 神经质 情绪化
Sidney，you made it
西德妮 你来啦
Hi。No I really mean that，Hi
嗨 我很认真的说 嗨
Do you girIs want a drink？
要喝东西吗？
Actually，we'll get it ourselves
我们自己来
I love those guys，are they still together？I haven't seen it in 3 weeks
他们还在一起吗？我三周没看了
No，they broke up again Sarah，found out that
没有 又分手了
Bailey slept with Gwen She dumped him like two episodes ago
莎拉发现巴利跟关儿上床 又像前两集那样把他甩了
I wish she'd get her shit together
真希望她心情好起来
Hold on，someone's calling
等等 有人插播
Omega Beta Zeta
奥比兹宿舍
Hello
喂
Yes？
什么事？
Who is this？
你是哪位？
Cici。Who's this？
西西 你哪位？
Who do you think？
你以为呢？
Ted？Where are you are you drinking？
泰德 你在哪？你醉了吗？
Hold on
等等
Ted's on the other line He sounds drunk，I'll call you back？
泰德好像醉了 我再打给你
That shit only calIs you when he's drunk。Don't go over there，Cici
他喝醉才打给你 别去找他
Alright，alright I'll call you back
好 我再打给你
Okay Ted，you sound loaded What's up？
泰德 你好像醉了 怎么了？
Who's Ted？
谁是泰德？
I'm sorry。My bad ears I thought you were someone else
对不起 我以为你是别人
That's okay。I am
没关系 我是别人
Who are you calling for nobody's here
你找谁？这边没人在
Where is everybody？
大家都去哪？
We're co-sponsoring the Acid Rain Mixer at the Phi Gamma Alpha tonight
我们今晚协办酸雨慈善会
Why aren't you there？
你怎么没去？
I'm sober sister I have to be here
我留守以便接送
in case a drunk sister calIs and needs a ride
喝醉的姐妹
That's too bad
太可惜了
Drink with your brain That's our motto
喝酒不闹事是我们的座右铭
Who are you calling for？
你打来找谁？
What if I said，you？
如果我说你呢？
What if I said goodbye？
如果我说再见呢？
Why would you wanna do that？
你干嘛要那么做？
Why do you always answer a question with a question？
你干嘛老用问题 来回答问题
I'm inquisitive
我喜欢打破沙锅问到底
Yeah，and I'm impatient Do you want to leave a message…
我没耐心 你要留话吗？
Do you want to die tonight，Cici？
你今晚想死吗？西西
Omega Beta Zeta
奥比兹宿舍
So was it Teddy？
是泰德吗？
No，it was some creep asshole trying to scare me
不 是个想吓人的变态狂
It's the movie STAB It's bringing out the crazies
都是电影招来一堆疯子
Shit
该死
What is it？
怎么了？
I heard a noise
我听到声音
Where？
哪里？
Upstairs
楼上
Shit
该死
Hello？Hello？
喂
Kill，kill，kill。Die，die，die
杀杀杀 死死死
Stop it
别闹了
I can't believe you're alone in that house
我不敢相信你一个人在
I don't think I'm alone
我觉得屋子里有人
I'm out of here
我要离开这边
You're breaking up。Where are you？
电话收讯不良 你在哪？
Outside
外面
Don't panic，sweetie Call Campus Security
别慌 打给校警
Okay
好
Campus Security
校警
Hi，I'm calling from
嗨 我是从…
Can't hear… Hello？Hello？Can you hear me now？
听得到了吗？
Hello？Shit
喂 该死
Campus Security
校警
Yes，I'm calling from…
喂 我是从…
I can't hear you。Hello？
我听不到 喂
I'm calling from the Omega Beta Zeta house。Someone's harassing me
有人在骚扰我 喂
Shit
该死
Jesus，Dawnie，you scared me
天哪 你吓死我了
I'm sorry。Did anyone call for me？
对不起 有人打来找我吗
What are you doing here？
你在这儿干嘛
I live here，remember？
我住这儿 记得吗？
I just thought you were going to the mixer
我以为你去聚会了
Yeah，I had to change So I'll be out of here now
我得换衣服 我要走了
Omega Beta Zeta
奥比兹宿舍
Cici there？
西西在吗？
Who's calling？
哪里找？
It's Ted
泰德
It's your ill-conceived boyfriend
你那无聊男友打来的
Okay，I'll see you later And don't forget to set the alarm
晚点见 别忘了设定警报器
Hello，Ted
喂 泰德
You wish it was Ted Don't forget to set the alarm
别痴心妄想泰德会打来 别忘了设警报器
Hello？
喂
No！No！Please！No！
不…求求你 不要
Everyone thinks Sororitys are about blowjobs，but it's not true
大家以为姐妹会的人 喜欢口交
We only promote safe condom sex
不 我们只是提倡 安全性关系
We're about love respect and responsibility
我们讲求爱 尊重与责任
Harmonica style is okay，right？
吹萧也没关系 对吗？
Yeah
对
Cocktails？
鸡尾酒？
What took you so long？
你怎么拖这么久？
And you know Derek is a Delta Lambda big brother
德瑞克是我们的大哥哥
And we like to keep it all in the family
我们要有一家人的感觉
You girIs have really given me a lot to think about。Thanks
你们真的教我太多了 谢谢
It's working
有效
Hey baby，wanna dance？
宝贝 想跳舞吗？
I'dlove to
我很想…
With that tall wide shouldered Fraternity boy
跟那个高大宽肩的男生跳
That hurts
真伤人
Empire Strikes Back Better story，improved effects
帝国大反击 剧情效果都进步
Not a sequel。Party of a trilogy completely planned
不算续集 那是三部曲之一
I like those little furry things
我喜欢那些毛茸茸的小东西
Ewoks…They blow
受不了
How you doing？Good
你怎么样？
Are the Twits being nice to you？
傻妞们对你好吗？
Painfully nice
好得让人痛苦
I take it will not being pledging Delta Lambda Zeta
我想你不会入会了
I think not
没错
Crushed
干杯
Hey guys！Something is up at Omega Beta Zeta。The Police are everywhere
宿舍出事了 到处都是警察
Hurry
快
What a way to break up a party
真扫兴
Shit I should have brought my drink
我应该带酒才对
So it's definitely not suicide
这绝对不是自杀罗
Thank you
谢谢
Gale，Hi。You're just getting here？
盖尔 你才刚来吗？
It's not good It's a single victim。Sorority girl
真不好 被害者是单身一人 姐妹会的女孩
I've got to go。I've got a deadline
我得走了 我快截稿了
Joel，let's go
乔 走
In a minute
马上
It's happening again，isn't it？
又发生了 是不是
You would love that，wouldn't you？
你很高兴吧！不是吗？
Better hurry，Gale you might get scooped
快去呀 独家会被抢走哦
Move it，Joel
快点 乔
Yeah，I have to be honest with you
我得跟你老实讲
I'm not cut out for this。I was brought here to do an interview
我真的不行 我是来采访的
Not see 「Faces of Death 14？」
不是来看杀人片
Do not fuck with me
别他妈的扯东扯西
Come on，get your jacket Let's get you home
来 拿外套 我送你回家
Yeah
好
Are you about ready？
好了吗？
Almost
马上好
Hello？
喂
Hello Sidney，Remember me？
喂 西德妮 记得我吗？
What do you want？
你想干嘛？
I want you，it's show time
我要你 好戏上场了
Then why don't you show your face you fucking coward
那你怎么不露脸？他妈的孬种
My pleasure
真是我的荣幸
Derek
德瑞克
Sidney
西德妮
Derek
德瑞克
It's me！It's me！Are you okay！You okay？
是我 没事吧
Derek，don't
德瑞克 不要
Sid
西德妮
Dewey
杜威
The killer's in there，and Derek
杀手跟德瑞克在里面
Are you alright？
你没事吧
He went that way
他往那边跑了
Sidney，get in here
到里面来
Is everything okay？
都还好吧
He got me。He got me
他刺到我
Apply pressure to it
压住伤口
The Police are on their way
警察赶来了
Thanks for your cooperation
谢谢你的合作
Hallie，I'll be with you in a few minutes，okay？
我过几分种就来陪你
No problem
没问题
Easiest interrogation of my crime filled life
我犯罪生涯中 最简单的侦讯
I'm going to go get a cup of coffee You want？
我要去弄杯咖啡 你要吗？
You want some，Sid？
你要吗？西德妮
How you doing，are you all right？
你怎么样？还好吧
Not at all
一点也不好
You know，I knew this was coming I knew this wasn't over
我早就知道没完没了
You are not alone，Sid
你不会孤军奋战的
We're all here for you Alright。Whatever you need
不论你需要什么 我们都会陪你
Poor girl
死掉的女孩真可怜
I know，it's crazy
我知道 整件事都很疯狂
Derek could have been killed you know
德瑞克可能会被杀
But he wasn't。He's fine
但他没有 他没事了
He just need to realize that the 90's are no time to play hero
他该知道90年代 不能逞英雄
Why did he go back into that house anyway？
他为什么要回到屋里？
I went around to the back of the house，and ran into Sid there
我绕到屋后碰到西德妮
That's when she told me the killer was inside。So I went into see…
她说凶手在里面我就去看
You're lucky there is no nerve damage
你很幸运没伤到神经
You're going to have to take it easy though
这伤慢慢会恢复
So then you went back inside the house
然后你回到屋里
Yeah
对
No struggling he just cut you and ran away？
没打斗 他割伤你就跑了？
You're lucky he didn't kill you
他没杀了你就算你走运
Yeah，it's awfully convenient
对 要杀可容易的很
Say what？
你说什么？
Nothing。It's just a shame he got away so easily
没事 可惜轻易就让他逃走了
It's just a shame you got there too late
可惜你太晚到
Right after he disappeared
他走了之后才出现
Yeah，it is
是啊
We have three victims
有三名被害人
Maureen Evens，Phil Stevens
莫琳·艾文斯 菲尔·史帝文斯
Cici Cooper
西西·库伯
Is Cici the girl's real name？
西西是真名吗？
No，it's Casey。Casey Cooper
不是 是凯西·库伯
As in Casey Becker？
跟凯西·贝克一样？
Excuse me？
你说什么？
She was a young victim in Woodsboro
凯西·贝克是伍兹伯勒的被害人
As well as her boyfriend Steven Orth
她男朋友史蒂夫·奥斯也是
As in Phil Stevens
跟菲尔·史帝文斯一样
Maureen Evens。Maureen Prescott
莫琳·艾文斯 莫琳·普莱斯柯特
that's Sidney's mother
那是西德妮的母亲
Do you think someone's trying to duplicate Woodsboro？
你想有人 在抄袭伍兹伯勒案？
It looks like it
看起来像
I think you have a copycat on your hands，Chief
这案子真的是模仿案
Jesus Christ…
天哪
What are you doing to keep Sidney safe？
你要怎么让西德妮安全？
I've got my two best detectives guarding her
我派了最优秀的刑警 保护她
Do these guys have to follow you around everywhere？
这两人非得和你 寸步不离吗？
We're attached at the hip
我们是连体婴
How I am ever going to get you alone？
我要怎么才能跟你独处
To be honest，Derek，I think it would be best to…
老实说 我认为这样最好
your interest to stay as far away from me as possible
离我远点对你较好
Hope that was a off the cuff remark that holds no sub-text what so ever
别因为情绪不好就说气话
Actually，I mean it
其实我说真的
Look at you，you already got hurt
瞧你 你已经受伤了
I don't want to see that happen again
我不想再看到那种事发生
I'll take my chances
我运气没那么背
Derek，I'm serious This is serious
我说真的 这很严重
You are concerned with my personal well being。And not with…
你是担心我安危 还是不信任我
trusting me or anything。Right？
我猜对了吧？
Like I said，I just don't want to see you get hurt
我说了我不想看到你受伤
And I don't want to see you get hurt。Okay Sid？
我也不想看你受伤 好吗？
Take care，Miss Weathers
保重 韦瑟斯小姐
Dewey
杜威
Chief
警长
Hi，I'm headed over to admissions to do some leg work，You game？
我要去搜集资料 你要来吗？
I'm not here to write a book I'm here to help Sid
我可不帮你写书 我来帮西德妮
I wanna help her too
我也想帮她
And help myself，of course
当然也为了帮我自己
Come on，Dewey Smile just once，please
别这样 笑一个 拜托
I'll smile when I catch the killer
等我抓到凶手也会笑
Gale，Hi
盖尔 嗨
What about Sidney's father？Has he been ruled out as a suspect？
西德妮的父亲没嫌疑了吗？
He's out of the country on business that sounds a little fishy.
他出国了 这有点可疑
I'm not here to do your job Mrs Salt
你做你的调查 这和我无关
What about this ex-cop Dewey Riley？Kind of strange that he showed up
杜威呢 他的出现有点怪
What's he doing here？
他来做什么？
Dewey's a good guy Unlike some of us
杜威是好人 他和其他人不一样
Really？
真的？
If the killer is repeating what happened in Woodsboro
我只是觉得事件如果重演
It could be quite possible that killer could be from Woodsboro
凶手很可能是伍兹伯勒的人
Derek，do you think Sid would let me interview her for my documentary
你想西德妮会让我访问她吗？
Didn't she turn down 「Primetime Live」，「20-20」，and 「Dateline」
她婉拒各大电视和新闻媒体
But for you，yeah
但可以为了你的纪录片
Drop it
别闹了
I've been thinking about his whole murder thing
我在想谋杀的事
Have you checked out Randy？
你们查过兰迪没有？
What！
什么？
I know he's an innocent victim the first time around
我知道他是无辜受害者
But he's a little off You know what I'm saying？
但他有点怪 懂我意思吧！
Come on，Randy？The guy is harmless
兰迪不会伤害人
That's what they said about Damher
许多杀人魔也都被这么认为
Guys，keep it down，come on
小声点
What's up，Sid？
怎么了？西德妮
How's it going？
怎么了？
Where's the Secret Service guys？
保镖刑警在哪里？
Over there
那边
And which one is Kevin Costner？
哪个是凯文·科斯特纳？
The one on the right is Officer Richard
右边的是李察警官
He is a Capricorn Divorced，father of Two
魔羯座 离婚 有两个孩子
And the one on the left is Officer Andrews
左边的是安德鲁警官
He is a Gemini Single，but I think he's Gay
双子座单身 我想是同性恋
Derek，a penny for your thoughts？
德瑞克 你要说什么
This morning I woke up with this feeling
早上醒来我有个感觉
I didn't know how to deal with
不知如何面对
And so I just decided to myseIf I'dhide it to myself
于是我决定藏在心里
What is he doing？
他在干嘛？
Tom Cruise，Top Gun 1986
汤姆·克鲁斯 悍卫战士
Derek，don't…
德瑞克 不要
Don't do this
别这样
I think I love you
「我想我爱你」
Isn't that what life is made of？
「人生不就如此」
Though it worries me to say I've never feIt this way
「我担心 我不曾有这种感受」
I think I love you！So what am I so afraid of
「我想我爱你 我怕什么」
I'm afraid that I'm not sure of A love there is no cure for
「我怕不确定无药可救的爱」
I think I love you Isn't that what life is made of
「我想我爱你 人生不就如此」
And though it worries me to say it I've never feIt this way
「我担心 我不曾有这种感受」
Believe me，you don't have to worry
「相信我 你不用担心」
I only want to make you happy
「我只想让你快乐」
And if you say，hey go away！I will
「如果你叫我走 我会走」
But I think I'dbetter stick around and love you
「但我还是留下来爱你」
Until you find happiness
「直到你找到快乐」
Let me ask you，do you think Do you really love me？
让我问你 你真的爱我吗？
Because I think I love you
「因为我想我爱你」
Come on，people let's show a little love
各位同学 展现一点爱
Don't worry，Sid
别担心 西德妮
I know things are a little crazy
我知道情况有点疯狂
Isn't that a big，Frat faux-pas？
那不是兄弟会的大忌吗？
Yeah，that is a big no-no
对 万万不可
See，you're not suppose to give your Greek letters to your girl
不能把兄弟会信物送给女朋友
No shape，way or form
不得以任何形式或方式
The Brothers are gonna kick his ass But it's tradition
兄弟会修理他 但这是传统
It's tradition
那是传统
It's good luck It will protect you
那是好运 它会保护你
So tell us about this part you're getting rave reviews for
谈谈你这个广受争议的角色
I play this girl，Sidney Prescott
我演西德妮·普莱斯柯特
Who discovers her boyfriend is a crazy serial killer
她发现她男友是疯狂杀人狂
who also killed her mother the year before that
还在前一年杀了她母亲
So what kind of research did you do for the part？
你为角色下了多少功夫
I read the book…
我看了书…
They get Tori Spelling to play Sid
他们竟让托莉·史培林演西德妮
And they cast Joe-Blow Nobody to play me
演我的却是无名小卒
At least you get David Schwimmer
至少演你的还有些名气
I get the guy who drove Jane Seymour's stagecoach…
演我的是简·西摩尔的马车夫
in one episode of Doctor Quinn
其中一集是奎因医生
Let's take a peak at the movie…
以下是托莉演出的片段
Billy，you scared me what are you doing here？
比利 你吓到我了 你干嘛！
They let me go Sid I didn't do it。I'm innocent
我获释了 我是清白的
I know
我知道
Why won't you let me touch you？
你为什么不让我碰你？
Look，I've been going through a lot lately，Billy
我最近碰到太多事
Sid，I think you just need to deal with that and move on
你要勇敢面对它好好活下去
When my mom left my dad，I accepted it.That's the way the cookie crumbles
我也要接受我妈离开我爸
Moms leave
妈妈总会离开我们
Yeah，your mom left town。She's not buried in the cemetery somewhere
她离开镇上 不是埋在地下
My mom's dead and she's never coming back。Ever
我妈死了 再也不会回来
Stupid
笨
I love scary movies
我最爱看恐怖片
I'll wait for the video
我会等录影带上了再说
Okay，let's get down to business
好 谈正事
The way I see it someone's out to make a sequel
我看马上就有人要怕续集
You know，cash in on all the murder movie hoopla
我们得搜集更多谋杀电影
So it's our job to observe the rules of a sequel
所以我们要了解续集电影规则
Number one the body count is always bigger
第一 死得更多
Number two，the death scenes are always much more elaborate。More…
第二 死得更难看
blood，more gore。Carnage Candy Your core audience just expects it
观众会期待更精彩的场面
And number three…
第三
If you want your sequel to become a franchise never，ever…
想让续集卖座就千万别…
How do we find the killer，Randy？That's what I want to know
我只想知道怎么找到凶手
Let's look at the suspects
我们看看嫌犯
There's Derek the obvious boyfriend Hello Billy Loomis
德瑞克 就像她前任男朋友
The guy's pre-med and his pity-me service wound
他学医 用那点小伤搏取同情
conveniently missed every major vein and artery
那小伤完全避开了主要血管
So you think it's Derek？
你认为是德瑞克？
Let's assume the killer or killers have haIf a brain
假设凶手是有点小聪明
He's not a 「Nick at Night」 re-run type of guy
他就不会去重蹈覆辙
He wants to break some new ground Right？
他要另外再找新点子
forget the boyfriend It's tired。Who else do we got？
别管男友 太老套了 还有谁
Mickey The freaky Tarantino film student
米奇 那个昆汀·塔伦提诺迷
But if he is a suspect So am l。So let's move on
如果他是 那我也有嫌疑 再想
Let's not move on Maybe you are a suspect
等一下 搞不好你正是嫌犯
If I'm a suspect，you're a suspect
我是嫌犯 那你也是
You have a point
有理
Okay，let's move on
好 继续
Hallie
海莉
Sid's roommate？
西德妮的室友？
Serial killers are typically white males
典型杀人狂是白种男性
That's why it's perfect。It's sort of against the rules，but not really
这样才完美 违反规则
Mrs。Voohies was a terrific serial killer
黑人小姐是绝佳的杀人狂
And there's always room for Candy Man's daughter
总得给黑人小姐一个机会
She's sweet。She's deadly She's bad for your teeth
她甜美 所以危险
Come on，Randy These kids are your friends
拜托 这些人是你朋友
Who do you think is the killer？
你认为谁是凶手
How about Gale Weathers？
盖尔怎么样？
Gale，a killer？
盖尔 凶手？
Why not？
为什么不？
She's vicious enough
她心眼够坏
She's an opportunist
她只是个机会主意者
Isn't it conceivable She's planning her next book
想不到吗？她在筹备下一本书
That's what reporters do Dewey。They stage the news
记者最会炒新闻了
No，Gale's a lot of things but Gale's not a killer
不 盖尔绝不会是凶手
Just because you're sweet on her
你太迷恋她了
I'm not
我没有
Please，this is me talking，Randy
拜托 我是兰迪哎
The unrequited love slave of Sidney Prescott
我是单恋西德妮的爱情奴隶耶
I know all about obsession
我知道什么是执迷不误
and pain
这很痛苦
And you've got your love scar to prove it
你有爱的伤疤来证明
And so do you
你也有
Man，what is with that limp anyway？'Cause you were stabbed in the back
你怎么会跛脚？因为你被刺到背
Severed nerve
因为神经被切断
Look，Gale's no killer
但盖尔绝不是凶手
Okay，okay，whatever you say
好 随便你怎么说
But if she's not a killer she's a target
她不是凶手 就是目标
Joel，let's get some establishing shots
乔 拍一些背景画面
Gale，can we talk for a second？
可以谈一下吗？
What is it？
什么事？
Look，I'm a little confused here I mean，with your track record
我搞不懂 以你过去的遭遇
Why would you want to be here when the killer strikes again？
现在又发生凶案 何必在这逗留
I mean granted，I should have read your book。Before I took this job
我应该在接下工作前 看你的书
But，I'm reading it now，and whoa
我正在看 哇
I read what happened to your last cameraman
才知道前一个摄影师的下场
The guy got gutted
他被开膛剖肚
Now me？I would do what any rational human being should do
我现在要做一般人会做的事
Which is get the fuck out of here
那就是走人
First of all，he wasn't gutted I made that up
他没被开膛剖肚 那是我编的
His throat was slashed
他是喉咙被割断
Gale，gutted-slashed the guy ain't in the union no more
反正他已不在人世了
It's a job，Joel
这是工作
And like every job there's a few drawbacks
所有工作都有一些风险
You're a professional cameraman You've got to act like one
你是专业摄影师就敬业点
Yeah，but I want to report the news I don't want to be the news
我只想报新闻 不想变成新闻
Besides，「Brothers」 don't last long in situations like this
黑人在这种情况下 都活不久
This is national television
这是全国电视网
Think about it This is a big chance for you
这是成名的大好良机
The story is monumental Don't you want to be a part of that？
你不想参与 轰动全国的报导？
Come on，I need you I cannot do this without you
我需要你 没你我做不到
Good，come on Let's get some work done
好 干活吧
Yeah，let's go get killed
好 准备去被宰吧
We've been through this before
我们先前谈过了
You know what I think of your potential as an actress
你知道我认为 你很有表演潜力
I know it's just that with the murders
我知道 只是命案的事
And the movie，and my life
那部电影和我的人生都一团乱
I do know how difficuIt it is for you
我知道这对你很困难
Gil，I just don't think I can do it
我觉得我做不到
The battle for the soul is fought in the forum of the art
你必须利用艺术来化解忧虑
You're a fighter Sid That's why you're here
你是斗士所以你在这儿
That's why this is your major
所以你会主修戏剧
Yeah，I'm a fighter
对 我是斗士
I didn't hear that
我没听到
I'm a fighter
我是斗士
I don't believe you
我不相信你
I don't
我不信
I'm a fighter
我是斗士
Okay
好
So at the risk sounding like a college drama teacher
我知道这样说太像大学戏剧老师
if you have pain around this type of material，use it
但我要利用这种痛苦
This is your role，Sid
这是你的角色
Cassandra is one of the great tragic visionaries of literature
卡珊德拉是悲剧性 的预言家
She saw it all coming
她全预料到了
The wars，the murder，the madness
战争 谋杀 疯狂
She knew she was cursed
她知道她被诅咒
It was her fate and she embraced it
那是她的宿命 她拥抱它
None of us can avoid our fate But as an artist…
宿命难逃 但身为艺术家
you can honestly face it and fight it
你能诚实的面对它 对抗它
You're good
你真行
There's no understudy I'm desperate
没替角 我一定要说服你
You can do this
你做得到的
Okay，everybody gather around third act，one last time
好 大家集合 第三幕
Cue the music
音乐来
Behold the dreaded fate of Troy
看 特洛伊城可怕的恶运
That once stood proud and light upon the hilIs of Sparta
曾伫立照亮斯巴达的山坡
Now shrouded in the deathly smoke of ruin
如今笼罩在废墟的烟雾中
Her royal children picthed from her walls
其王室子女从墙上被抛下
Her people driven through her ruins
子民从废墟中被驱赶而过
And now，alone in Fate's cruel isolation stands Cassandra
卡珊德拉孤独站在残忍宿命中
Her kingdom，family and friends
她的王国 家人和朋友
driven to the gate
被赶到大门口
No crime against God or man have I committed
我未犯下反神之罪
Save to speak the truth
除了说出真相
And each hideous vision born from my mind has come to pass
我心中的可怕预言皆已降临
Troy has fallen
特洛伊沦陷了
Not by my hand，or wish
不是藉我的手或愿望
But as I foresaw
而是如我预见的
So now，Fate's vengeful eye…
如今宿命复仇之眼
is fixed…on me
盯上了…我
Tell us O Cassandra
告诉我们 卡珊德拉
where has the sweetness of life gone？
生命的甜美如今何在
What stays fate's hand from striking now at three？
如何让宿命之手不攻击你
Alright，hold it
好 暂停
Hold it
暂停
Everyone take five
大家休息一下
Sidney？
西德妮
Sid。Your escort has arrived
你的护花使者来了
Derek，how long have you been here？
德瑞克 你来多久了？
I just got here。Is everything okay what's going on？
刚到 还好吧？怎么回事？
What happened to Mickey？
米奇呢？
We swapped。He had to edit
我们调换 他要剪接
You get me instead。What happened？
我来接 怎么了？
Derek，don't…
不要…
I just I need to be alone right now。Okay？
我现在需要独处 好吗？
Being alone is not the answer，Sid
独处不是办法
Yeah，I think it is I need some distance
我的意思是我需要距离
Well，do I get a say in this？
我还能说什么？
No
别说了
I guess I'm supposed to be understanding
我知道我该体谅你
Yeah
没错
You got it
没问题
Alright，let's just assume that the killer is repeating Woodsboro
如果凶手在重演 伍兹伯勒血案
Yes？
喂
I have to call you back
我再打给你
That doesn't explain Sidney's attack
那他干嘛要攻击西德妮
Sidney wasn't killed in Woodsboro
她在伍兹伯勒又没被杀掉
It wasn't for a lack of trying
她只是逃过一劫
The killer is trying to finish what was started
凶手想做个了结
Sid is under protection，right？
西德妮有人保护 对吗？
Yeah
对
What？
干嘛？
Tell Bob I'll call him back
跟鲍伯说我会打给他
When did she start smoking？
她几时开始抽烟了？
Ever since those nude pictures on the lnternet
从网路上出现 她的裸照开始
It was just my head It was Jennifer Aniston's body
那是我的头 詹妮弗·安妮斯顿的身体
Anyway，you're forgetting something
我们一定忘了什么重点
In Woodsboro，there were more victims before the home stretch
在伍兹伯勒有更多被害人
Tatum，my cameraman，Himbry
泰坦 他是我的摄影师
Time out。See I don't need to be hearing about no dead cameraman
暂停 我不想听摄影师的事
Now I'm warning you guys，I'm a verb away from vacating these premises
我警告你们 我要闪人了
I'm gonna go get me some coffee，donuts，Prozac
我去买咖啡 甜甜圈和镇定剂
See if I can find some crack special K，Eggs
看能不能找到一些快乐丸
I'll be back when you guys start talking about something little…
等你们谈完我再回来
more 「Save By The Bellish」 Alright？
好吗
He seems a little shaky
他好像很害怕
Don't worry about him
别担心他
If the killer is following a pattern
我们要找出凶手杀人模式
then maybe we can figure out who is next
看谁是下一个受害者
That wouldn't follow the pattern we were all involved in Woodsboro
没有模式 我们都被追杀过
It could be anyone of us
我们任何一个 都可能被害
Okay so what do you want to do，Bonehead？
好 那你想怎样？
You just want to sit here and wait for who drops next？
等着看下一个是谁吗？蠢蛋
I don't know，phonehead
我不知道 电话小姐
Gale's not here
盖尔不在
I'm not interrupting anything，am I You three look deep in thought
打搅你们吗？你们好像很烦恼
Have you ever feIt a knife cut through human flesh…
尝过刀子割肉
and scrape the bone beneath？
的滋味吗？
It's him
是他
Who？
谁？
The killer！He can see us
凶手 他看得到我们
Just keep him on the phone
别让他挂电话
What do you want me to say？
我要跟他说什么？
I don't know。Just keep him talking。Come on，Gale
不知道 让他继续讲 走
What are we doing？
我们要干嘛？
Look for somebody with a cell-phone
找有行动电话的人
So，what's your favorite scary movie？
你最喜欢哪部恐怖片？
You'll never find me
你们绝对找不到我
What do you care let them have their fun
你怕什么？让他们去玩
So，what's up？
那你要干嘛？
What's your favorite scary movie？
你最喜欢哪部恐怖片？
Show girls。Absolutely frightening
「美国舞娘」吓死人了
What's yours？
你呢？
Sorry…
对不起
What's your problem？
你要干嘛？
Wait，let me guess The House on Sorority Row？
等等 让我猜 惊魂夜
Dorm that dripped Blood？Splatter University？
滴血校舍 溅血校园
Graduation Day？Final Exam？
结业日 期终考
Am I close？
我很接近你吗？
Closer than you think
比你想像中近
Too slow you Geek Do you want to die？
猜错了 你想死吗？
Is that the best you can do？
这已经是你最厉害 的招数啦？
Because Billy and Stu were much more original
第一集的凶手 都比你有创意
Who's this？
你是哪位？
Gale Weathers author of the Woodsboro Murders
伍兹伯勒血案的作者盖尔
Who？
谁？
Okay，he's got to be around here someplace
好 他一定在这附近
He's just playing with us
他在耍我们
White male suspect nine o'clock
白种男性嫌犯 九点种方向
My clock or your clock
我的表或你的表？
Your clock。Go around the back
你的表 绕到后面
Why are you even here Randy？You'll never be the leading man
你来干嘛？你绝不会是男主角
Fuck you
去你的
No matter how hard you try you'll never be the hero
你再努力也当不了英雄
And you'll never ever get the girl
而且永远无法得到西德妮
Shit！Sorry…
妈的 对不起
Wrong guy，dead boy
倒霉鬼 死人
Oh yeah？Let's redirect mister
是吗？想重新再杀人一次吗？
「I'm so original」
我很有创意哦
What the hell are you doing？
搞什么鬼？
Sorry，Beg your pardon
抱歉 对不起
Where's your innovation？
你的创意在哪？
Why copy-cat two High School looser-ass dick heads
干嘛模仿两个 高中窝囊废
Stu was a pussy-ass wet rag
斯图是没种的娘娘腔
And Billy Loomis！Billy Loomis！What the fuck？
而比利·鲁米斯 搞什么
Jesus！What a rat-looking homo repressed mama's boy
獐头鼠目性压抑又黏着妈妈
Why not set your goaIs higher You want to be one of the big boys？
目标订高点 想当大人物吗？
Manson？Bundy？OJ？
辛普森 高天民 陈进兴
Where's Randy？
兰迪在哪？
I don't see him
没看到他
Randy
兰迪
What's going on？
怎么回事？
Who broke my window？
谁把我的车窗打破了
Did your computer just freeze？
你的电脑不动了吗？
You have an instant message that's all。Just hit Alt-M
你有讯息 按ALT一M
Yeah，but I'm not signed on
可是我还没上线
Someone here in the library all the terminaIs are connected
所有终端机都有连线
（你今晚会死）
He's here
他在这边
Get her away from the computer Sid，it's probably just a sick joke
「警察救不了你」 把她带开 可能是病态的玩笑
Wait right here，okay
在这边等
Sid，are you okay？
你还好吗？
Cotton？
卡顿
Can we talk for a second？
可以谈一下吗？
This isn't a good time
现在不是时候
Come on Sid，you sent me to prison
别这样 是你害我坐牢的
It's been over a year for you you can give me two minutes
坐一年牢 不能给我两分种
Cotton，I'm sorry。Everyday I'm sorry。I don't know how to apologize
我很遗憾 我不知该如何道歉
Don't be sorry，sorry-shmory。I have a solution to all our problems
别遗憾 我给你道歉的方式
What are you talking about？
你说什么？
First of all，forget Gale Weathers
别管盖尔 她什么都不懂
She doesn't get it。She doesn't see the story between you and me
她不明白你我之间的故事
She wouldn't see the story if it smacked her in the side of the head
即使凶手杀了她 她都不知为什么
Which brings me to my point Who calIs me out of the blue？
重点是你知道谁找我吗？
Diane Sawyer。Believe me Sid I was as shocked as you are
黛安·索耶 够吓人吧
If you and I go on the air together She will give us the entire hour
我们可以有 整整一小时的节目
We are talking Prime Time，Sid You，me and Diane Sawyer
而且是黄金时段
Cotton，I can't
我做不到
If this is about money It's not like we're not getting paid
他们付我们一人
$10000 dollars each
一万块
Not to mentioned what I got going on the side with the #900 number.
更不用说我热线电话的收入了
I know。You don't like the press
我知道你不喜欢媒体
I know that and I respect it But Sidney
我很尊重你 可是西德妮…
It's Diane Sawyer。Hello？
这是黛安·索耶
She's a class act。This could be some very，very heavy exposure
她很大牌 曝光率会很高
I'm sorry
对不起
Look，between the movie，& the book People know the truth
大家都从电影和书知道真相
Let's get on our lives There's been enough exposure
曝光够多了 你还要怎样
Why would you want anymore？
不能平静地生活吗？
Why？I don't know，Sidney
要怎样？我不知道哎
Maybe because I fucking deserve a little exposure
我想更出名吧！
Come on Sidney，you drag my name through the mud
别这样 是你先毁掉我的名誉
Everybody thinks I'm some kind of Psycho killer
让大家都以为我是变态凶手
& all I'm asking for is one little fucking Diane Sawyer interview
我只是要求做个访问
To maybe give my side of the story straight
让我澄清我的罪名
I don't think I'm being unreasonable in that request。Do you honestly？
这不会太不近人情吧？
I'm sorry，Cotton，but no
抱歉 不行
You are sorry
你抱歉
I bet you're real sorry，Sidney
我敢说你真的很抱歉
What's your angle，Sidney？
你到底想怎样？
Lovable and fucked up Sidney Prescott
可爱倒霉的 西德妮·普莱斯柯特
Everybody's favorite little victim
最受欢迎的受害人
What are you doing？
你们做什么？
Jesus！I'm not Billy Loomis
天哪 我不是比利
she killed him，he's dead，remember？
他杀了她 他死了 记得吗？
Run it by me one more time Will you？
再跟我讲一遍 好吗？
Why did you attack Sidney Prescott
你为什么攻击西德妮？
There was not attack We were talking，very heatedly
哪有攻击 只是谈得很激烈
Miss Prescott and I have a very complicated past
西德妮和我 有段复杂的过去
I didn't think that was a crime
和她有口角不算犯罪
No，but homicide is
没有 若有谋杀意图就有罪
Then book me。Book me
那就收押我
Okay？Look I don't know about homicide
谋杀的事我不懂
But you defiantly got me for raising my voice in a public library
但你们因为 我在图书馆喧哗而抓我
We're dealing with four murders here。You watch your mouth
这是四起命案 讲话当心点
It shouldn't have been Randy It should have been me
不该杀兰迪 应该杀我
I should call his mother
我应该打给他母亲
Sid，I already made that phone call
我打过了
Are you okay？
你还好吗？
Stop treating me like glass，Dewey I'm not going to break
我没那么脆弱 轻易被击倒
It's okay to break
有时脆弱一点没关系
It's not going to happen
我不会让它表现出来
You better hope your alibi is air-tight
你最好有充分的不在场理由
Could I please remind everyone here that I'm an innocent man
容我提醒各位我是清白的
Don't you watch TV 「Current Edition」
你们不看2100全民开讲吗？
That was a very insightful program On which it was made abundantly…
很犀利的电视节目
clear that I'm an innocent man
这节目明白指出过我的清白
So until you find me standing over a dead body with a knife in my hand
除非你们亲眼目睹 我持刀杀人
I think you better treat me with the rights and privileges
我想你更好的对待我的权利和特权
accorded to every citizen in this country
赋予每个公民在这个国家
Is there some problem with the word innocent
还是你们不了解 什么叫无辜？
I don't know It's a big one，Chief？
很重要的字 警长？是吧
What's going on？
怎么回事？
We're going to let him go
我们得放他走
Why？
为什么？
We don't have anything on him
没证据关他
Sign here
在这边签名
Gale
盖尔
enjoying the show？Cops are funny
戏好看吗？警察真可笑
What do you think you're doing？
你在做什么？
Waiting for my 15 minutes of fame You can understand that，can't you？
等你访问我十五分种 懂吧
Don't do anything stupid，Cotton
别做傻事 卡顿
You were so instrumental in my freedom
你帮了大忙让我自由
You're not having character doubts now，are you？
你不会是后悔吧
Sidney，if you change your mind…
西德妮 如果你改变心意…
Come on，take a hike
好了 让开吧！
Sorry about that。What a creep
真遗憾遇到这个怪胎
We're going to take you somewhere safe，Sid
我们带你到安全的地方
Yeah，where's that？
好 哪里？
I don't know But I'll be there with you
不知道 但我会陪着你
We should get going
应该走了
Take you by the dorm and you can pack some things
我们会载你到宿舍 收拾东西
We've issued a campus lock-in this evening
警方今晚封锁了校园
No one is allowed out after dark。Okay.
天黑后不准有人进出
Who's doing this，Dewey？
会是谁这么做？
If not Cotton，then who？
除了卡顿还有谁？
I don't know，Sid but I'll find him
不知道 但我会找到他
Any leads，Gale？Do you think the killer will come after you？
有线索吗？凶手会找上你吗
How does it feel to be on the other side of the news？
换你变成新闻主角感觉如何？
Cotton！Are you still a suspect？
卡顿 你还是嫌犯吗？
It's all been a huge misunderstanding
那是天大的误会
Cotton have you been officially released？
你正式获释了吗？
Gale，hold on a second How about a photo？
盖尔 等等 拍张照吧
No？You look great
不要？你很上相哎
How you holding up，Gale？It must be scary…
你还好吗？
knowing somebody's out there waiting，watching，enjoying all this
被窥伺的感觉 一定很恐怖吧！
How does that make you feel？
你做何感想…
Look，local woman！I know you hold me up as your career template
我知道你把我 当做踏脚石
And it give you some sort of charge to challenge me
挑战我让你想利用我 一步登天
But give it a rest
还早的很呢！
You're right。I'm sorry
你说得对 抱歉
It was，the wrong time。I'm sorry
时候不对 对不起
What's going on？
怎么回事？
Let's see，for starters they impounded my van
你瞧！他们扣押了我的车
it's now an official crime scene Thanks to you
多亏你 它成了命案现场
Here is your footage
这是你的影片
Enjoy。See ya wouldn't want to be ya
你自个儿慢慢看 我要走了
Joel，I need you
乔 我需要你
No，you need to have your head examined
不 你需要检查脑袋
I feel bad，Dewey
我觉得很惨
I feel really bad
我觉得惨透了
I never say that because I never feel bad about anything
我从不认为我会这么惨！
But I feel bad now
但我现在觉得很惨
Is this just another brilliant Gale Weathers Performance？
这是盖尔分身 的真情演出吗？
There's no cameras here I just want to find this fucker
又没人在拍我 我只是想找凶手
I really do
我真的想
Me too
我也想
Can I give you a hand？
我能帮你吗？
What's in here？
里面是什么？
Just some crowd footage that Joel shot
乔拍的群众影片
Wait a minute
等一下
If the killer really is watching and relishing every minute
若凶手 真的无时不刻的窥伺
Then he would be here on these tapes，right？
那他就会在带子上 对吗？
At each crime scene
在每个犯罪现场
It's worth a look
值得看一看
Definitely worth a look
肯定值得一看
This way
这边
Dubbing room
配音室
editorial。Video archive
剪接室 录影档案
It's locked
锁住了
Can you pick it？
你能撬开吗？
That would be breaking and entering
那就是私闯
No shit
真的
There's got to be a VCR around here somewhere
这附近一定有录影机
What's in there？
那里面是什么
Now we're getting somewhere
有进展了
Perfect
太好了
Let's start with this one
从这卷开始
Sorry
抱歉
I'm sorry
对不起
Did I hurt you？
弄痛你没？
No
没有
You're a money hungry，fame seeking
你贪图名利 原谅我直说
and forgive me for saying mediocre writer
也是笔法二流的作家
who's got a cold storage shed where her heart should be
而且冷酷无情
No offense intended
别见怪
You're cute when you're angry
你生气的样子很可爱
I was being rude
我不是有意的
Dewey，I'm sorry
杜威 很抱歉
I never meant to hurt you
我从没想过伤害你
Really
真的
I should be studying you know I got a bio…
我要学习你知道 我得到了生物…
Dewey
杜威
Sorry
对不起
That's not my footage
那不是我的影片
Fuck you
去你的
No matter how hard you try you'll never be the hero
你再努力也当不了英雄
And you'll never ever get the girl
而且永远无法赢得芳心
Wrong guy，dead boy
找错人了 死猪
Stay here
别走开
Dewey，don't！
杜威 不要
Dewey
杜威
There's no one there
那边没人
Fuck
操
Gale！Gale？
盖尔 盖尔
Gale
盖尔
No
不
So…
那么…
Listen，Sid
听着 西德妮
Wait up
嘿 等等
She's fine
她没关系
I'm her therapist
我是她的心理医师
Bye，Derek
拜 德瑞克
We better get going
我们最好走了
When this is all over
等这一切过去了
I'll still be here
我还会在这儿
You！Prepare to Die
你 准备受死吧
You gave up your letters
你把兄弟会的信物送人了
So romantic
好浪漫
Totally so Greek
绝对希腊风味
That's cold
好冷
Who do you love，baby！Sidney
宝贝 你爱谁？
Did you say my Omega Kappa Beta brothers？
你是说爱我们兄弟会吗
No，I said Sidney
不 我说爱西德妮
So where you taking us anyway？
你们要带我们到哪？
If we told you we'd have to kill you
说出来 我们就得杀了你们
Don't ask，don't tell
别问 别讲
Out of the car，you fucker
下车 你这个混蛋
Get down back there
趴下
Pull it over，you son of a bitch I'll blow your fucking head off
王八蛋 我会让你脑袋开花
Is he dead？
他死了吗？
I don't think so
我不认为
No，he's still breathing
他还在呼吸
Is he dead？
他死了吗？
Oh God，I think so
天哪 我想是
How you suppose to get out of here？
怎么离开这里？
We are not，it is a cop car
不可能 这是警车
Help me with this We're jammed up against the wall
帮我弄
Oh my God
我的天
Don't… Sid…
不要 西德妮 不要
God，I hate this shit
我讨厌这种事
Oh my God，don't do that again
我的天 别再来一遍
Through the window
从窗子
Shit
该死
It's jammed，you're going to have to go through the front
卡住了 你得从前面出来
No fucking way
休想
Hallie。Do it…Hallie，do it
海莉 快点
Okay，that's good
好 很好
Come on，let's go
走吧
Hallie
海莉
What？
干嘛？
I want to know who it is
我想知道是谁
No，Sid，come on，please
不 西德妮 求求你
I'm going back
我要回去看
Look，look，stupid people go back Smart people run
智障才回去 有点脑袋都会逃
we are smart people。So we should get the fuck out of here
我们有脑袋 快逃命啦
Hallie，I'm sick of running
我逃烦了
If we know who it is it's all over
不查明凶手会没完没了
We can just get the police
可以找警察啊！
Yeah，and when we come back he'll be gone
等警察来他早跑了
It will only take a minute I have to
一下就好
Sid，no Sid，come back
西德妮 不要 回来
Sid，come back
西德妮 回来
Shit
该死
What？
怎么了？
He's gone
他不见了
What？
什么？
Gale？
盖尔
Get away from me
离我远一点
No，no This isn't want it looks like
不…不是你想的那样
I found Dewey。I tried to help him
我发现杜威 我想救他
Gale！Wait！Gale
盖尔 等等
Shit
妈的
Help me
救命啊！
Give me the phone
电话给我
I was in the middle of a story
我正在做报导
I have your God damned story
我有你要的报导
What's the matter？
怎么了？
Operator，this is an emergency get me the police
这是急事 帮我接警察
What's happening？
发生什么事？
The killer is Cotton fucking Weary
凶手是卡顿·威瑞
Cotton Weary？
卡顿·威瑞？
Hello？
哈罗
Hello！
有人吗？
Hello？
God。Derek
天哪 德瑞克
Derek
德瑞克
Thank you，thank God，Sid
谢天谢地 西德妮
T thought I was going to be up there until opening night
我以为我会在这 待到公演当晚
Shit。Who tied these？We have to get out of here
谁绑的？我们得离开这边
Brothers got me，Sid
兄弟们抓住我
Derek，he's after me He killed Hallie
他在追我 他杀了海莉
What are you talking about？
你在说什么？
The killer。He's here
凶手在这边
Where？
哪边？
Right here
就是这边
You're fast，Sid
你动作很快嘛！
Get me down
把我弄下来
I wouldn't do that if I were you
换成是我 我不会那么做
You really want to trust your boyfriend？
你当真要信任 男朋友吗？
Don't you know history repeats itself。Sid
你不知道历史会重演吗？
Mickey
米奇
Surprise，Sidney
没想到吧！西德妮！
What the fuck？
搞什么？
Since Derek here disappeared on my ass
都是德瑞克不配合好
I've been on my own all the fucking night
害我整晚都一个人
Thanks a lot，partner
多谢你哦 伙伴
You mother fucker！Sid，he's crazy
王八蛋 他疯了
You know me better than that
你知道我不会那样的！
Sid，I've got to have a partner
我必须有搭档
I couldn't possibly done this alone
我一个人是做不来的
Derek
德瑞克
No，Sid。No…
不 西德妮 不…
It's okay，Derek。We got her
没关系 我们抓到她了
Sid，he's lying
他在说谎
Sid！I'm telling you，Sid。Untie me
西德妮 我跟你说 帮我松绑
Boyfriend，killer？Boyfriend，killer？
男朋友？凶手？
Sid，the man is lying！Untie me Sid，untie me
他在说谎 把我松绑
What do you think，Derek？Sidney experiencing some dejavu？
你觉得怎样？似曾相识吗？
I am going to fucking kill you Fucking kill you
我会杀了你 杀了你
You are dead！Dead！
你死定了
I'm so sorry
真对不起
I never would have hurt you
我绝不会伤害你
Never
绝不会
You should really deal with your trust issues，Sid
你得搞清楚 谁才值得信任
I mean，poor Derek
可怜的德瑞克
He's completely innocent and such a nice guy too
很无辜 这么好的人
He's bright，funny and handsome
聪明 风趣又英俊
Decent singing voice and he was going to be a doctor
歌声还可以的准医生
This was the kind of boy you'd like to take home to Mom
你会想带回家 给妈妈看的男孩
If you have a Mom
如果你有妈
Fuck you
去你的
Oh！So vulgar
喔 这么凶！
Billy let you talk to him this way？
比利让你那样讲话吗？
Billy was a sick fuck Just like you
比利跟你一样变态！
No，Billy was a sick fuck who tried to get away with it
不 比利想逃避制裁
Mickey is a sick fuck who wants to get caught
而米奇想被抓到
Yeah！I've got my whole defense Planned out
我的法庭抗辩 都计划好了
I'm going to blame the movies
我可以把罪过 推在电影头上
Pretty cool，huh？It hasn't been done before
很酷吧 以前没人做过
You see this is just the beginning A prelude to the trial
现在只是审判前的开场白
That's where the real fun is.'Cause these days it's all about the trial
审判才是我的重头戏
Can you see it？Effects of cinema violence on society
因为电影暴力 对社会的影响
I'll get Dershovitz Cochran to represent me
我会请大律师代表我
Bob Dole on the witness stand in my defense
鲍勃多尔会在证人席为我辩护
Hell，the Christian Coalition will pay my legal fees
基督教联盟会付诉讼费用
It's airtight，Sid
太完美了
I'm an innocent victim
我是无辜的受害人
You're a psychotic
你疯了
Yeah that will be our little secret
对 那是我们的小秘密
People love a good trial
民众喜欢精彩的审判
It's like theater they're dying for it
跟戏剧一样 他们爱死了
Now I've worked hard to give the audience what they want
我必须满足观众
That's what Billy was good at He knew，it's all about execution
比利真厉害 他知道这跟手法有关
Yeah？you are forgetting our thing about Billy Loomis
是吗？你忘了一件比利的事
What's that？
什么事？
I fucking killed him
我杀了他
Sid。You got a Linda Hamilton thing going
西德妮 你想学银幕女英雄
No，no，it's nice。I like it
这样好 我喜欢
Now who's doing that！
是谁搞的鬼！
Could that be the mystery guest waiting in the wings？
是久候的神秘佳宾吗？
Told you I had a partner，Sid Surprise cameo just for you
我说过我有拍档 真相揭晓！
Gale
盖尔！
Mrs Loomis？
鲁米斯太太
What？
什么？
Billy's mother
比利的母亲
Nice twist，huh？Didn't see it coming，did you？
够曲折吧！敲破头也猜不到吧！
It can't be I've seen pictures of you
不可能 我看过你的照片
Lose sixty pounds and a lot of work later
减肥60磅 花了不少功夫
It's called a make-over You should try it
这可以算是次美容，你也可以试一下
You look a little tired there yourself，Gale
你看起来有点疲倦
So you two were in this together？
你们俩一伙的？
Yeah，had to have financing Tuition's expensive
我需要资助 学费很贵
Deb' there，my backer
黛比支持我
We met on the lnternet Psycho-website
我们在神经病网站认识的
classifieds
极机密的
There's only an estimated 97 active serial killers in the country today
据估计国内只有97个杀人狂
So Mickey here was quite a find Definitely one on the way up
找到米奇真棒 他前途无量
All he needed was a little guidance and nurturing
只需要一点引导和教育
As only a mother can do
这就是母爱的光辉
Told you this was going to work
我跟你说会成功吧
Wait till the trial It's gonna rock
等到法庭审判时 会更惊天动地
Mickey there's not going to be a trial
米奇 不会有审判的
Gale
盖尔
Two birds。One stone
一石二鸟
Mickey was a good boy
米奇是个好孩子
but my God that old blame the movies motive
他老把罪过推给电影
Did you buy that for a second？
你相信吗？
Poor boy was completely out of his mind
这可怜的孩子彻底疯了
And you're not？
而你没有？
No。I'm very sane
不 我很清醒
My motive isn't as nineties as Mickey
我的动机没像米奇那么90年代
Mine is just good old fashioned revenge
我是老套的复仇记
You killed my son
你杀了我儿子
And now I kill you。And I can't think of anything more rational
我杀你是再合理不过的事
You're never going to get away with this
你逃不过制裁的
Of course I will
当然会
Everything is traceable back to Mickey
一切线索都追溯到米奇身上
lncluding the cop-gun he used to kill everybody
包括他用来杀人的警察配枪
But let's just suppose you had gotten hold of the other cop's gun
假设你拿到另一把枪
You chased Mickey and there was a big shoot out。Big scuffle
你追米奇 一场枪战扭打
And you shot Mickey Killed Mickey dead
你杀了米奇 米奇挂了
But not before he got off one shot at you
但他先前对你开了一枪
Okay。Have I covered everything？Are there any questions？
我都顾到了吗？有问题吗
Any comments？You know what though
你还问我意见啊！
Who gives a flying fuck anyway
反正谁在乎
Let them try and track down the second possible killer
让他们去追第二个凶手
Debbie SaIt doesn't exist
黛比·索特根本不存在
You're as crazy as your son was
你跟你儿子一样疯
What did you just say？
你说什么？
Was that a negative disparaging remark about my son？About my Billy！
那是藐视我儿子的话吗？
No，Billy was a good boy
不 比利是个好孩子
Billy was perfect you did a bang-up job，Mrs。Loomis
比利很完美 你教得很好
It's not wise to patronize a woman with a gun，Sidney
少拍我马屁 我手中有枪
Randy spoke poorly of Billy and I got a little knife happy
兰迪贬低比利 捅他真爽
I was a good mother
我是个好母亲
You know what makes me sick
你知道我最恨什么吗？
I'm sick to death of people saying that it's all the parent fault
我恨人家说 都是父母的错
That it all starts with the family
这一切都始于家庭
Want to blame someone？Why don't you blame your mother？
如果要怪 怎么不怪你妈
She's the one that stole my husband And broke up my family
偷走我老公 破坏我的家庭
And then you took my son
然后你又抢走我儿子
You don't know what it is to be a mother
你不知道当母亲的滋味
To raise a child To teach him！And guide him
养育孩子 教他 开导他
And abandon him
遗弃他
Isn't Mickey supposed to be dead？
米奇不是死了吗？
Don't you fucking move God damn it
不准动 可恶
Cotton
卡顿
Okay，okay。Everybody slow down
好 大家慢下来
I have had a very very bad day
我今天非常非常倒霉
& I would like to know exactly what the fuck is going on here！Sidney？
我想知道怎么回事 西德妮
Cotton，meet Billy Loomis' mother she's the killer
这是比利的母亲 她是凶手
What？
什么？
And who's that？
那是谁？
The other killer，Mickey
另一个凶手 米奇
Okay
好
Look，Cotton
卡顿
Shut up
闭嘴
So…Hi
那么…嗨
You're not Debbie Salt，are you？
你不是黛比·索特对吗？
You're not with the Post Telegraph？
你不是邮电报的人
No，but I can still help you Cotton
没错 但我还是能帮你
You don't need her Let me killer her
你不需要她 让我杀了她
As long as she's alive，you're never going to be the lead story
她活着你就当不了主角
That's what you really want Isn't it，Cotton？
那是你要的 不是吗？
If you really want the spotlight Just let me killer her。Right now
想要曝光出名 就让我杀了她
Then you're the only survivor You're the star
你是唯一生还者 你是明星
She sent you to prison for a year
她害你坐了一年牢
Personally I think it's rather poetic
听起来很顺耳吧
No，Cotton，don't you listen to her
卡顿 别听她的
It's quite a predicament here isn't it，Sid？
很难做决定 不是吗？
Cotton
卡顿
I mean she makes a good point
她说得很有理
Let me think about this。Maybe you should too。I will bet you that…
我会考虑 也许你也该考虑
Diane Sawyer interview is looking real good right about now
我敢说黛安·索耶访问 有希望了
Consider it done
没问题
That was intense
好险
Hey，Sidney…
嘿 西德妮
I want you to know that I would never ever do anything to hurt you
我绝不会做出伤害你的事
Cotton，give me the gun
卡顿 枪给我
Yeah。Okay。Sure。Take it
好 当然 拿去
Sidney，we should probably talk about what exactly happened here
我们或许应该谈谈事发经过
Get our stories straight？
在我们的故事里
Can somebody get me out of here
谁来拉我上去
Gale。Are you alright？
盖尔 你还好吧？
I've been shot，of course not
我中枪了 当然不好
Give me your hand，Gale
手给我
Jesus Gale，you scared the crap out of me
天哪 你吓死我了
There isn't anybody else down there is there？
下面没人了吧
No
没有
So much for reporting from the trenches，huh？
在跌落舞台报导到此为止
Shut up，Cotton
闭嘴
How bad is it？
严不严重？
Bounced off my rib
子弹从我的肋骨弹开了
Jees，Gale you have more lives than a cat
天哪 你的命比猫还长
Give me one of those？
给我一把枪
Is she dead？
她死了吗？
I don't know。They always come back
不知道 他们常会复活
Just in case
以防万一
That about wraps it up，Chief
差不多了 警长
Okay，Frank
好
Take it easy，you've got a couple broken ribs there
轻点 断了几根肋骨
Gale。You alright？
盖尔 你没事吧
Joel？
乔
I'm back
我回来了
I was thinking maybe we could get the scoop like in the old days
我想我们或许能抢个独家
You're Gale Weathers at Windsor College
盖尔在温莎大学报导
We have a live one here
这边有个人还活着
Dewey
杜威
I can't believe you are alive
我不敢相信你活着
Are you okay？
没事吧
Gale
盖尔
You hang in there
你撑着点
I'm coming with you
我跟你去
Can you tell us what you saw？
告诉我们你看到什么
Can you tell us what happened in there？
里面发生了什么事
Sidney，can you tell us how it feeIs to be a hero？
西德妮 请谈谈当英雄的感受
Talk to Cotton
他才是英雄 卡顿
He's the man you want to interview He's the hero
他才是采访对象 他是英雄
What happened in there？Why are you a hero？
发生什么事？为何你是英雄
Details，please
请说细节
Look guys，no one wants to give you this story more than I do
没人比我更想提供这个故事
Unfortunately，there's time and a place。lndeed a price for everything
可惜要看时间地点和价码
So feel free to call me
随时打给我
Come on，Cotton Tell us something
卡顿 说一点嘛
I'll tell you one thing
至少有一件事我可以说
It'll make a hell of a movie Thank you
这故事会拍成很棒的电影 谢谢